

Mohemed Khaled Ghaffari Web developer

ElMenzah 1 , Chammbi street , Tunis Tunisia

med.khaledghaffarii@gmail.co

54091984

 $\red{https://khaledghaffarii.yercel.app} https://khaledghaffarii.yercel.app$

Contact



tunis,Tunisie

My name is Khaled, Graduated from the Higher School of Technology in Tunis, recently web developer. ready to integrate a company where I will be able to live daily experience and improve my knowledge by integrating a professional team.

Social networks

@/khaledghaffarii

in @/mohamed-khaled-ghaffari-850a4a167/

Education

Web development 3w-Academy Urban Center-North tunis ariana From November 2019 to April 2020

Java programming Ghazela Technology ElGhazela

September 2019

six days of training: discovery of the procedural and object-oriented Java algorithm

Bachelor's Degree, Embedded System Higher Institute of Medical Technology of Tunisia April 9th street Tunis ,Tunisia

From 2016 to 2018

Skills

HTML,CSS	
Tailwind css , Bootstrap	
JavaScript,jquery	
Nextjs,Reactjs	
React Native	
firebase, Mysql	
Git,GitLab	

Professional experiences

React and React Native Developer, remote Shadows-me Riyadh, Al

Bahah ,Saudi Arabia

Since August 2021

Development of a chocolate mobile application for a DALLA &

HALLA store

tools: react-native ,tailwind css and firebase

development of a fashion web application for the Saudi company

Loom

tools: Nextjs ,tailwind css and firebase

Mobile developer EPPM Silver Street, Fatma Building Lake gardens,

Tunis, 1053, TN

From January 2021 to May 2021

Individual project:

Development of a Dashboard mobile application to keep all projects

under control

Technologies used:

Front end part:

React native expo and Cli

Javascript

Back end part:

node js, mysql, phpMyAdmin, Postman

React developer intern DevNet Elmenzah9, tunis

From July 2020 to December 2020

individual project:

development of a restaurant web application.

Technologies used:

 $front\ end\ part:\ reactjs,\ react-router,\ redux,\ javaScript\ css3,\ bootstrap$

4, sweetalert

back end part: laravel 5.8, phpMyAdmin, Postmanfirebase (database,

Cloud Firestore, hosting,) git / gitLab

team work:

application site: jawi.tn

technologies used:

front end part: css, bootstrap 4 reactjs, react-router javaScript,

Jquery git / gitLab

IT Maintenance Technician Trustlt Elghazela Technological Pole

From October 2019 to December 2019

End of study internship Insight Télématique montplaisire, tunis

From January 2018 to June 2018

Design of a prototype of geolocation equipment

Biomedical Technician Intern AirLiquide charguia1, tunis

From July 2017 to August 2017

Electronic Technician Intern Mongi-Ben-Hmida Neurology Hospital

tunis,elrabta

From August 2016 to September 2016